Contact

- elmansoura
- 01270284534
- abobakrmohamed 2438@gmail.com
- in abubakr mohamed
- https://github.com/abobakr1001

Personal information

Birthdate 1/6/1997

Residence elmansoura / egypt

Nationality egyption

Social status single

military situation exempt

Interests

- music
- Reading
- sports

language

- ✓ arabic
- english

PERSONALSKILLS

Self confident

Like to in a group

Work under pressure

ABOBAKR MOHAMED

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

OBJECTIVE

I'm a hard-working front-end developer with experience in angular framework My goal is to produce high quality, clean code with very careful attitude to details. I work, using dev tools and systems I always make sure that your Website is responsive

Education

Elmansora university
 Commerce college | 2016 - 2019
 good

Experience

seen solutions

| 12/2022 - limit now

Wecancity

1/2022 - 12/2022

skyline

skyline | 2/2021 - 12/2021

grand technology

part time

trainee of route

route | 4/2018 - 8/2018

I worked in some projects with route academy

trainee of itshare

itshare | 6/2019 - 9/2019

I worked in some projects with route academy

Skills

Skill group

html5 css3 javascript jquery ES6 typescript



Skill group

bootstrap sass git/github angular+2 angular material rxjs ngrx c# firebase



Projects

E-COMMERCE

https://e-commerceee.netlify.app/

this site about e-commerce you can add to card anything, delete this order

, update it and add product . this site used by framework Angular $\rm html$, sass , bootstrap , TS

MOVIE

https://movie26.netlify.app/ web site angular about trending films you can create account, login, logout, see trending films and details all films.

COOKING

https://cooking22.netlify.app/ this site by framework Angular , API , TS , SASS , HTML , Bootstrap

MOVIE 2

https://abobakr1001.github.io/movie/ this site by framework Angular , API , TS , SASS , HTML , Bootstrap

ENGINEERING PROJECT

https://dapper-macaron-201119.netlify.app/ not finished yet

WATCHES

https://watches-new.netlify.app/
this site by html/css js bootstrap without framework